I'm a flat earther and I live in New
England I'm a flat earther in New
England because I can see the pole star
which is the North Star and I understand
how important it is that the North Star
never ever moves now I own telescopes
that track the stars and we'll track the
moon and whatever you want it to track
and you can point it at the North Star
and it will never ever move it won't
budge it won't go anywhere which is
telling me we are not endlessly spinning
1,000 M an hour at the equator 6600 700
mph around the Sun and Chasing the Sun
through the Galaxy 500,000 plus milph
it's kind of a ridiculous concept when
you understand that so being a New
Englander I really wanted to understand
what's going on in the winter time and
in the summertime why do we get a winter
how come how come the northern
hemisphere is cold when the southern
hemisphere is Hut vice versa and that
makes a heck of a lot of sense when you
understand the Flat Earth map in the
Flat Earth theory the whole idea makes
way more sense now when you also
understand that Flat Earth has been
encoded in the Bible many times it says
that the Earth is a circle a circle is
two-dimensional and flat an airplain it
flies on a plane a plane is flat okay
when you circumnavigate the ocean all
circumnavigations have gone from east to
west or west to east never north to
south why because a circle you're
circumnavigating you're navigating in a
circle you don't navigate in a ball you
don't go around a ball you don't go
around a sphere on an airplane never
ever when you're flying an airplanes you
go around a ball it's total utter
nonsense now what is going on in New
England on the summer solstice okay
which is July 20th what's happening is
the sun is actually C it always circles
like it says in the Bible and it's
circling is close to the Northern
Hemisphere as it's going to get now
after the solstice it starts to actually
head out and circle out towards the
southern hemisphere which is why our
days start to get shorter and our nights
begin to get longer because the Sun is
going further away and the reason why
it's not bright all the time on a flat
Earth is because light only travels so
far okay if you have a flashlight and
you keep walking eventually you're not
going to be able to see the light it's
the same idea with the sun okay
eventually you can't see it which
explains time zones and everything okay
the Flat Earth explains everything this
spinning globe is total otter nonsense
now after the Equinox the fall equinox
okay which is September 20th September
21st depending on where you live what
that means is that it's equal day and
equal night so you have daylight from 6
to 6 night time from 6: to 6 there are
only two equinoxes there's the Spring
Equinox and the fall equinox okay so
that's the fall equinox now the next
event to happen and this event is a big
one because Christianity has encoded
this event forever and this is Christmas
the birth of the Son of God it's not the
birth of a man named Jesus it is however
it can be considered the birth of the
son why is that that's because if you
track the sun on sun dials you'll notice
every day the sun sets different
location from the previous day by one
degree on a Sund dial and you can track
this all of a sudden on December 22nd
23rd and 24th 3 days in a row it sets in
the same exact location the ancient
people realized this and they were
shocked they couldn't believe it because
the son to them was the son of God it
was God's son and God's son dies because
anything that doesn't move for 3 days
was considered dead and they realized
that the sun was going away to the
southern to the Southern Hemisphere and
for those 3 days it goes as far away as
it's going to go now on December 25th
the sun actually begins to come back
from the Southern Hemisphere and it
begins to make its way back to the
Northern Hemisphere so that we can again
have our summer solstice in the summer
now that's on December 25th we still the
sun is still far away and it's still F
closer to the southern hemisphere than
the northern hemisphere which is why our
winter is still going to be cold and
brutal now until the Equinox okay the
the sun crosses that Equinox now here we
go again religions encoding this the
reason why on the Spring Equinox Jewish
people celebrate the Passover okay where
they blow a Ram's Horn and they
sacrifice a ram it's all symbolical
because Aries is the ram
Aries is the constellation during that
time of the year and the Sun is crossing
over the equator essentially it is
beating Aries it is Conquering Aries the
RAM and the sun is coming back to the
Northern Hemisphere now again this has
been encoded in religions and so much so
when you start to learn that it's it is
the it's more than a theory okay it's
encoded in everything and then they lie
about it so that it keep Keeps Us in the
dark why because we are the uneducated
we are considered the profane and by
uneducated I mean us Americans that went
to college and went to school we are
uneducated because we are not in the
group okay it's that simple we are not
in the group we don't know what the
group talks about what the group
understands and what the group learns
and let me tell you it's a hell of a lot
different than the crap that we learn
and until you do your research you're
not going to know that you have to
understand you have to do your research
all right this is taking me a long time
to learn because there's so many
different topics and so many things but
I'm telling you right now if you get to
the point and this is easy if you go
outside and you start to learn where the
North Star is you can start to find the
big and little dipper right now you can
go outside and you can see right now
you'll be able to see Taurus really
beautifully you'll be able to see Orion
really beautifully and you can see the
three stars on his belt and all of that
if you can look up out at night and you
can start naming stars and knowing where
things are understanding the concepts of
that Saturn is in tus in that you know
all these things if you can start to
understand this you will start to
realize we are not on a ball endlessly
spinning through outer space that's all
I got to tell you but this is my opinion
I love you all and I hope you all stay
warm in this this winter stay safe and I
love everybody I'm just here to teach
people to teach people things to teach
people that there's another side to the
story and to show them that there are
other theories that make a hell of a lot
of sense I love you all